<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CheckMirrors</title>
    <description>checkmirrors school of motoring. Learn to drive in Yorkshire. Driving lessons from qualified instructors. From just £25 per hour. Pass plus options. York and Leeds.</description>
    <link>http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 19:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 19:33:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Congratulations to Harriotte Clemet from York who passed with Sarah, second time with only 4 x minors</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;” Sarah is an amazing driving instructor, she’s kind, brilliant and made me feel so calm throughout my driving experience. I would definitely recommend checkmirrors”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/testimonials/testimonial/2017/01/10/harriotte-clemet-pass.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/testimonials/testimonial/2017/01/10/harriotte-clemet-pass.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Testimonials</category>
        
        <category>Testimonial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Congratulations to Rob Ferguson who passed with Nick on 9th January 2017 at York. 1st time</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Rob said “Just passed first time with Nick and cannot say enough good things about him. Very calm influence, great teaching style and you couldn’t ask for a more qualified teacher. I would recommend Nick to anyone and I’ve already got my younger brother learning with him and I’m sure my younger sister will learn with him as well as a result. I felt very safe in his capable hands and credit my passing to him. Thank you Nick!”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/testimonials/testimonial/2017/01/09/rob-ferguson-pass.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/testimonials/testimonial/2017/01/09/rob-ferguson-pass.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Testimonials</category>
        
        <category>Testimonial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Congratulations to Seb Swenson who passed on 4 January 2017 with Sarah. First time with 11 minor faults</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Seb said:  “Experienced, knowledgeable, helpful and honest. I had a great instructor that helped both my wife and I pass our tests and it was well with every penny.  I don’t think “thanks” is enough to convey the level of appreciation I’m feeling right now, but the contribution of tough love, honest feedback and patience was just what I needed to pass.
Thanks so much for everything. I’d recommend the company and my instructor particularly to anyone looking to learn or just refresh”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/testimonials/testimonial/2017/01/04/Seb-Swenson-pass.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.checkmirrors.co.uk/testimonials/testimonial/2017/01/04/Seb-Swenson-pass.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Testimonials</category>
        
        <category>Testimonial</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
